crosswordgiant.com 2017-12-17

# Privacy Policy | CrosswordGiant.com

### **Introduction**

Your privacy is essential to us. At CrosswordGiant.com, we believe that privacy is a top priority. We know that you care about the way information about you is used and shared. Thus, we provide this Privacy Policy to summarize our procedures and practices as regards to information collection and use. By visiting CrosswordGiant.com, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy and hereby accept the procedures and practices stated in this herein.

### **Scope**

This Privacy Policy applies only within this website and other pages where this policy appears. This would describe and explain how we take care and handle your personal information you shared to us. By accepting the Privacy Policy, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

### **Collection & How Use**

If you attempt to use the services and applications of our website and or choose to provide information to us, this website shall collect Personal Information from you. This information includes, but is not limited to: Internet Protocol Address, Service Provider, Browser Type, Full Name and Email Addresses. Once collected, we will store your information for record keeping purposes.

### **Disclosure**

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place.

### **Cookies**

CrosswordGiant.com may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors.

### **Security**

All collected information is stored in a technically and physically secure environment. While we use SSL encryption to protect Sensitive Information online, we also do everything in our power to protect PII (including Sensitive Information) off-line. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect our end-users' personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

### **Third Parties**

We provide links to Web sites outside of our web site, as well as to third party Web sites. These linked sites are not under our control, and we cannot accept responsibility for the conduct of companies linked to our website. Before disclosing your personal information on any other website, we advise you to examine the terms and conditions of using that Web site and its privacy statement.

### **Changes & Amendments / Notification of Changes**

CrosswordGiant.com reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy at any time. All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Website. Please check the Website periodically for any changes.
